Guide to the Creative Time Archive 1973-2006 MSS.179
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Slides
  - Public/Private - citywide, 1992 (Box Binder AA, Folder Sleeves AA5-AA6)
  - Transitions, Inc. - citywide, 1992 (Box Binder AA, Folder Sleeve AA7)
  - Sacrificial Ornament - Municipal Art Society, 1992 (Box Binder AA, Folder Sleeve AA8)
  - Art in the Anchorage 9 - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1992 (Box Binder BB, Folder Sleeves BB1-BB12)
  - A Surreal Soap Opera - 30 Lincoln Center Plaza, 1992 (Box Binder CC, Folder Sleeves CC1-CC2)
  - Two Spirits Speak Out - Grand Central Terminal, 1992 (Box Binder CC, Folder Sleeve CC3)
  - Accountability? - NYC, Chicago, Los Angeles, 1992 (Box Binder CC, Folder Sleeve CC4)
  - Day Without Art: We Interrupt This Program… - citywide (via television), 1992 (Box Binder CC, Folder Sleeves CC5-CC9)
  - Higher Ground - St Patrick Youth Center, 268 Mulberry Street, 1993 (Box Binder DD, Folder Sleeves DD1-DD2)
  - Use Mass Transit 2 - citywide (via billboard), 1993 (Box Binder DD, Folder Sleeve DD3)
  - Victory Music Series - New Victory Theater, 209 West 42nd Street, 1993 (Box Binder DD, Folder Sleeves DD4-DD6)
  - 42nd Street Art Project - 42nd Street (slides subdivided within binder by artist), 1993 (Box Binder DD, Folder Sleeves DD7-DD15)
  - 42nd Street Art Project - 42nd Street (slides subdivided within binder by artist), continued from previous binder, 1993 (Box Binder EE, Folder Sleeves EE1-EE13)
  - In Honor of Allen R. Schindler - citywide, 1993 (Box Binder FF, Folder Sleeve FF1)
  - Universal Family Album - 30 Lincoln Center Plaza, 1993 (Box Binder FF, Folder Sleeves FF2-FF3)
  - Art in the Anchorage 10 - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1993 (Box Binder FF, Folder Sleeves FF4-FF9)
  - Underdevelopment in Progress/ 500 Years - Soho 20 Gallery, 469 Broome Street, 1993 (Box Binder FF, Folder Sleeves FF10-FF11)
  - Body Politics - Great Hall, The Cooper Union, 7 East 7th Street, 1994 (Box Binder GG, Folder Sleeves GG1-GG3)
  - Mass Transit 3: Hey Bozo… - citywide via billboard, 1994 (Box Binder GG, Folder Sleeves GG4-GG5)
  - Patina du Prey's Memorial Dress - 45 Greene Street, 1994 (Box Binder GG, Folder Sleeve GG6)
  - 1st Annual Roosevelt Park Summer Festival - Roosevelt Park, Houston to Delancey Streets, 1994 (Box Binder GG, Folder Sleeves GG7-GG9)
  - 42nd Street Art Project - 42nd Street, 1994 (Box Binder HH, Folder Sleeves HH1-HH9)
  - 20th Anniversary Celebration/42nd Street Art Project Opening - Apollo Theater, 1994 (Box Binder HH, Folder Sleeves HH10-HH15)
  - Art in the Anchorage 11 - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1994 (Box Binder II, Folder Sleeves II1-II5)
  - Lincoln Center Out-of-Doors: Wildstyle - 30 Lincoln Center Plaza, 1994 (Box Binder II, Folder Sleeves II6-II7)
  - Combat Zone - 110 Mercer Street, 1994 (Box Binder II, Folder Sleeves II8-II9)
  - Mama, I Thought Only Black People Were Bad - NYC, Los Angeles, 1995 (Box Binder II, Folder Sleeve II10)
  - Relax. Fly Mass Transit - citywide (via billboard), 1995 (Box Binder II, Folder Sleeve II11)
  - Art in the Anchorage 12 - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1995 (Box Binder II, Folder Sleeves II12-II19)
  - Brinca Charcos (High Waters) - Williamsburg, Brooklyn, 1995 (Box Binder JJ, Folder Sleeves JJ1-JJ3)
  - Lincoln Center Out-of-Doors: DJ Spooky - 30 Lincoln Center Plaza, 1995 (Box Binder JJ, Folder Sleeves JJ4-JJ6)
  - Building Sweeps - 64 West 128th Street, 1995-1996 (Box Binder JJ, Folder Sleeves JJ7-JJ10)
  - Time Capsule Book Launch - Paula Cooper and citywide, 1995 (Box Binder JJ, Folder Sleeves JJ11-JJ13)
  - New York Times Magazine Project, 1995 (Box Binder JJ, Folder Sleeve JJ14)
  - Art in the Anchorage 13 - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1996 (Box Binder KK, Folder Sleeves KK1-KK3)
  - Music in the Anchorage - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1996 (Box Binder KK, Folder Sleeves KK4-KK10)
  - Race for the Arts - Intersection of 10th Avenue and 36th Street, 1996 (Box Binder KK, Folder Sleeves KK11-KK14)
  - Winter Music - 2 Columbus Circle, Central Park, 1996 (Box Binder KK, Folder Sleeves KK15-KK17)
  - Rent-a-Body - citywide, 1996 (Box Binder KK, Folder Sleeve KK18)
  - Music in the Anchorage - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1997 (Box Binder LL, Folder Sleeves LL1-LL5)
  - Art in the Anchorage 14 - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1997 (Box Binder LL, Folder Sleeves LL6-LL7)
  - The Wish Machine - Grand Central Terminal, 1997 (Box Binder LL, Folder Sleeve LL8)
  - World Views - Deutsche Bank Building, 31 West 52nd Street, 1997 (Box Binder LL, Folder Sleeve LL9)
  - Exquisite Corpse - Saks Fifth Avenue, 611 5th Avenue [slide reference sheets from CT inserted before slides], 1997 (Box Binder LL, Folder Sleeve LL10)
  - Exquisite Corpse Benefit, 1997 (Box Binder LL, Folder Sleeve LL11)
  - 1-900-ALL-KAREN - international (via telephone), 1998 (Box Binder LL, Folder Sleeve LL12)
  - Gesture As Value - 55 Broad Street, 1998 (Box Binder LL, Folder Sleeve LL13)
  - El Mexterminator - citywide (slides subdivided within binder by location), 1998 (Box Binder MM, Folder Sleeves MM1-MM11)
  - El Mexterminator - citywide (slides subdivided within binder by location), continued from previous binder, 1998 (Box Binder NN, Folder Sleeves NN1-NN14)
  - Art in the Anchorage 15 - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1998 (Box Binder OO, Folder Sleeves OO1-OO10)
  - Between Dreams and History - Ludlow and Rivington Streets, 1998 (Box Binder OO, Folder Sleeves OO11-OO14)
  - Suits: The Clothes that Make the Man - Times Square, citywide, 1998 (Box Binder PP, Folder Sleeves PP1-PP16)
  - Day Without Art: Banner Project and 10 Web Action Tours - citywide (via internet), 1998 (Box Binder PP, Folder Sleeve PP17)
  - Art in the Anchorage 16 - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1999 (Box Binder QQ, Folder Sleeves QQ1-QQ20)
  - Music in the Anchorage - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1999 (Box Binder RR, Folder Sleeves RR1-RR6)
  - F.R.E.D. - citywide, 1999 (Box Binder RR, Folder Sleeves RR7-RR13)
  - Adolescence - citywide, 1999 (Box Binder RR, Folder Sleeve RR14)
  - The Intruder, 1999 (Box Binder RR, Folder Sleeve RR15)
  - Leap - 2 Columbus Circle, 2000 (Box Binder SS, Folder Sleeves SS1-SS2)
  - Tibor in Orbit - Times Square, citywide, 2000 (Box Binder SS, Folder Sleeve SS3)
  - Art in the Anchorage 17 - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 2000 (Box Binder SS, Folder Sleeves SS4-SS6)
  - Remix - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 2000 (Box Binder SS, Folder Sleeves SS7-SS9)
  - Teleport Diner - Stockholm, Sweden, 2000 (Box Binder SS, Folder Sleeves SS10-SS11)
  - DNAid Deli Cups - citywide, 2000 (Box Binder SS, Folder Sleeves SS12-SS13)
  - Music in the Anchorage - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 2000 (Box Binder TT, Folder Sleeves TT1-TT10)
  - DNAid Billboard / Bus Tour - citywide, 2000 (Box Binder TT, Folder Sleeves TT11-TT13)
  - Listening Post, 2001 (Box Binder UU, Folder Sleeve UU1)
  - Glassbox Project - proposed installation for Art in the Anchorage 2002, 2001 (Box Binder UU, Folder Sleeve UU2)
  - Clouds - citywide, 2001 (Box Binder UU, Folder Sleeve UU3)
  - Benefit, 2001 (Box Binder UU, Folder Sleeve UU4)
  - The 59th Minute: Superstar - Times Square, 2001 (Box Binder UU, Folder Sleeve UU5)
  - The 59th Minute: Cat Drinking Milk - Times Square, 2001 (Box Binder UU, Folder Sleeve UU6)
  - The 59th Minute: Shadow Procession - Times Square, 2001 (Box Binder UU, Folder Sleeves UU7-UU8)
  - The 59th Minute: ahistory - Times Square, 2001 (Box Binder UU, Folder Sleeves UU9-UU10)
  - The 59th Minute: Day Without Art - Times Square, 2001 (Box Binder UU, Folder Sleeve UU11)
  - Wink - Grand Central Terminal, 2001 (Box Binder UU, Folder Sleeves UU12-UU13)
  - Art in the Anchorage 18 - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 2001 (Box Binder UU, Folder Sleeves UU14-UU16)
  - Music in the Anchorage - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 2001 (Box Binder UU, Folder Sleeve UU17)
  - Welcome Back to Brooklyn - Empire Stores, 2001 (Box Binder UU, Folder Sleeve UU18)
  - Watercolor Distribution - Lower Manhattan, 2001 (Box Binder UU, Folder Sleeve UU19)
  - Time to Consider: The Arts Respond to 9-11 - citywide, Deutsche Bank, 31 W 52nd Street, 2002 (Box Binder VV, Folder Sleeve VV1)
  - Art on the Plaza 1: Primal Graphics - The Ritz-Carlton, 2 West Street, 2002 (Box Binder VV, Folder Sleeve VV2)
  - The 59th Minute: Fast Forward - Times Square, 2002 (Box Binder VV, Folder Sleeve VV3)
  - Focus on Peace, 2002 (Box Binder VV, Folder Sleeve VV4)
  - Consuming Places - 66 Water Street, Brooklyn, 2002 (Box Binder VV, Folder Sleeves VV5-VV6)
  - Music in DUMBO - 66 Water Street, Brooklyn, 2002 (Box Binder VV, Folder Sleeves VV7-VV9)
  - Tribute in Light - World Financial Center, 2002 (Box Binder VV, Folder Sleeves VV10-VV11)
  - Tap - Dia Arts Center, Whitney Museum, 33 E 17th Street, 449 W 14th Street, The Joyce Theater, 2002 (Box Binder VV, Folder Sleeve VV12)
  - Blur - The New School, 66 West 12th Street, 2002 (Box Binder VV, Folder Sleeve VV13)
  - The 59th Minute: Portraits - Times Square, 2002 (Box Binder VV, Folder Sleeve VV14)
  - Metapet - citywide (via internet), 2002 (Box Binder VV, Folder Sleeve VV15)
  - Holiday Light Show - Grand Central Terminal, 2002 (Box Binder VV, Folder Sleeve VV16)
  - Blue Moon - West St and Vesey St, Battery Park City, 2004 (Box Binder WW, Folder Sleeve WW1)
  - Art on the Plaza 4: Breath - The Ritz-Carlton, 2 West Street, 2004 (Box Binder WW, Folder Sleeve WW2)
  - Freedom of Expression National Monument - Foley Square, 2004 (Box Binder WW, Folder Sleeves WW3-WW4)
  - For New York City - citywide (via airplane), 2004 (Box Binder WW, Folder Sleeves WW5-WW6)
  - The 59th Minute: 3 Artists - Times Square, 2004 (Box Binder WW, Folder Sleeve WW7)
  - Dreamland Artist Club - Coney Island, 2004 (Box Binder WW, Folder Sleeves WW8-WW12)
  - The 59th Minute: The Forest - Times Square, 2004-2005 (Box Binder WW, Folder Sleeve WW13)
  - Dreamland Artist Club - Coney Island, 2005 (Box Binder WW, Folder Sleeves WW14-WW16)
  - Psychedelic Benefit, 2005 (Box Binder WW, Folder Sleeve WW17)
  - The 59th Minute: Conditions of Anonymity - Times Square, 2005 (Box Binder WW, Folder Sleeve WW18)
  - The Plain of Heaven - 820 Washington Street, 2005 (Box Binder WW, Folder Sleeve WW19)
  - For the City - Rockefeller Center, NYU Bobst Library, New York Public Library, 2005 (Box Binder WW, Folder Sleeve WW20)
  - Art on the Plaza - The Ritz-Carlton, 2 West Street, 2005 (Box Binder WW, Folder Sleeve WW21)
- Series IV: Photo Materials
  This series includes all negatives, transparencies, contact sheets, and photographic prints from the Creative Time Archive. These substantial holdings are ordered chronologically by year and separated by individual project. Projects have been separated according to different types of material—negatives, contact sheets, and prints (the few transparencies in the archive have been housed with the negatives). Photographic content primarily includes exhibition and performance documentation along with promotional photos, artist samples, and site/planning prints. Many prints and contact sheets include substantial annotation as to the project, artist, date, and photographer.
  - Negatives - Crafts in Action, Galleria at 100 William Street, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Contact Sheets - Crafts in Action, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Prints - Crafts in Action, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Negatives - Sail, 88 Pine Street, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Contact Sheets - Sail, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Prints - Sail, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Negatives - Ruckus Manhattan, 88 Pine Street, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Contact Sheets - Ruckus Manhattan, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Prints - Ruckus Manhattan, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Negatives - New York Sky Events: Neon Rainbow, Central Park, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Prints - New York Sky Events: Neon Rainbow, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Negatives - Anemones: An Air Aquarium, 88 Pine Street, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Contact Sheets - Anemones: An Air Aquarium, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Prints - Anemones: An Air Aquarium, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Negatives - Round: Sound for Concave Surfaces, US Custom House, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Contact Sheets - Round: Sound for Concave Surfaces, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Negatives - Custom and Culture 1; Custom and Culture 2, US Customs House, 1977, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Contact Sheets - Custom and Culture 1; Custom and Culture 2, 1977, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Prints - Custom and Culture 1; Custom and Culture 2, 1977, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Negatives - Butler's Lives of the Saints, 88 Pine Street, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Prints - Butler's Lives of the Saints, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Prints - Downtown Drive-In, Edison Parking Lot, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Negatives - Art on the Beach 1, Battery Park City Landfill, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Contact Sheets - Art on the Beach 1, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Prints - Art on the Beach 1, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Prints - Custom and Culture 2, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 286)
  - Prints - Downtown Drive-In 2, Edison Parking Lot, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Prints - The Artist at Work in America, Hotel Vitosha, Vodenicharski Restaurant, Sofia, Bulgaria, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Negatives - Art on the Beach 2, Battery Park City Landfill, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Contact Sheets - Art on the Beach 2, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Prints - Art on the Beach 2, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Negatives - Masstransiscope, Myrtle Street Subway Station, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Contact Sheets - Masstransiscope, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Prints - Masstransiscope, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Negatives - Breaking-In, First Precinct House, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Contact Sheets - Breaking-In, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Prints - Breaking-In, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Contact Sheets - Projects at the Precinct, First Precinct House, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Prints - Projects at the Precinct, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Negatives - Windspun, Hunter's Point, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Contact Sheets - Windspun, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Prints - Windspun, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Negatives - Art on the Beach 3, Battery Park City Landfill, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Contact Sheets - Art on the Beach 3, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Prints - Art on the Beach 3, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Negatives - Principles in Perspective, Chamber of Commerce, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Prints - Principles in Perspective, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Prints - Principles in Perspective, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 287)
  - Negatives - Art on the Beach 4, Battery Park City Landfill, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Contact Sheets - Art on the Beach 4, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Prints - Art on the Beach 4, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Print - Art on the Beach, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 288)
  - Contact Sheets - Projects at the Chamber, Chamber of Commerce, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Prints - Projects at the Chamber, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Negatives - Art in the Anchorage 1, Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Contact Sheets - Art in the Anchorage 1, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Prints - Art in the Anchorage 1, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Negatives - Art on the Beach 5, Battery Park City Landfill, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Contact Sheets - Art on the Beach 5, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Prints - Art on the Beach 5, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Contact Sheets - Walk In Theater for Pedestrians, Thurgood Marshall Courthouse, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Prints - Walk In Theater for Pedestrians, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Contact Sheets - Art on the Beach 6, Battery Park City Landfill, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Print - Art on the Beach, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 289)
  - Prints - Art on the Beach 6, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Contact Sheets - Touch Sanitation, Marine Transfer Station, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Prints - Touch Sanitation, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Prints - National Maritime Historical Society building photographs, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Contact Sheet - Benefit, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Negatives - Creative Time staff, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Contact Sheets - Creative Time staff, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Prints - Creative Time staff, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Negatives - Art in the Anchorage 2, Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Contact Sheets - Art in the Anchorage 2, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Prints - Art in the Anchorage 2, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Negatives - Art on the Beach 7, Battery Park City Landfill, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Contact Sheets - Art on the Beach 7, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - Negatives - Art on the Beach, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 290)
  - Prints - Art on the Beach 7, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - Prints - A Drop in the Bucket, Franklin Street, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - Print (from ink drawing) - Art on the Beach, [1985] (Box 22, Folder 291)
  - Contact Sheets - B. Holden to Diderot, US Courthouse, 40 Foley Square, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - Prints - B. Holden to Diderot, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - Contact Sheets - Art in the Anchorage 3, Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 78)
  - Prints - Art in the Anchorage 3 (continues in subsequent folder), 1986 (Box 16, Folder 79)
  - Prints - Art in the Anchorage 3 (continued from previous folder), 1986 (Box 16, Folder 80)
  - Prints - Art in the Anchorage, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 292)
  - Prints - Jazz in the Anchorage, Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 81)
  - Negatives - Performance in the Park 1, Central Park Bandshell, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 82)
  - Contact Sheets - Performance in the Park 1, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 83)
  - Prints - Performance in the Park 1 (continues in subsequent folder), 1986 (Box 16, Folder 84)
  - Prints - Performance in the Park 1 (continued from previous folder), 1986 (Box 16, Folder 85)
  - Negatives - Performance in the Park 2, Central Park Bandshell, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 86)
  - Contact Sheets - Performance in the Park 2, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 87)
  - Prints - Performance in the Park 2 (continues in subsequent folder), 1987 (Box 16, Folder 88)
  - Prints - Performance in the Park 2 (continued from previous folder), 1987 (Box 16, Folder 89)
  - Negatives - Art in the Anchorage 4, Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 90)
  - Contact Sheets - Art in the Anchorage, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 293)
  - Contact Sheets - Art in the Anchorage 4, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 91)
  - Prints - Art in the Anchorage 4, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 92)
  - Contact Sheets - Art in the Anchorage 4 Party, Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 93)
  - Prints - Art in the Anchorage 4 Party, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 94)
  - Negatives - Art on the Beach 8, Hunter's Point, Queens, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 95)
  - Contact Sheets - Art on the Beach 8, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 96)
  - Prints - Art on the Beach 8 (continues in subsequent folder), 1987 (Box 17, Folder 97)
  - Prints - Art on the Beach 8 (continued from previous folder), 1987 (Box 17, Folder 98)
  - Contact Sheets - In the Winter Garden: Relay, World Financial Center, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 99)
  - Prints - In the Winter Garden: Relay, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 100)
  - Contact Sheets - In the Winter Garden: Anggrek, World Financial Center, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 101)
  - Prints - In the Winter Garden: Anggrek, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 102)
  - Prints - Misfortunes of Desire Acted Out…, Shea Stadium Parking Lot, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 103)
  - Negatives - Art in the Anchorage 5, Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 104)
  - Contact Sheets - Art in the Anchorage 5, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 105)
  - Prints - Art in the Anchorage 5, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 106)
  - Negatives - Art on the Beach 9, Hunter's Point, Queens, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 107)
  - Contact Sheets - Art on the Beach 9, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 108)
  - Prints - Art on the Beach 9, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 109)
  - Negatives - 15th Anniversary Halloween Party, Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 110)
  - Contact Sheets - 15th Anniversary Halloween Party, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 111)
  - Prints - 15th Anniversary Halloween Party, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 112)
  - Negatives - UP Tiempo!, El Museo del Barrio, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 113)
  - Contact Sheets - UP Tiempo!, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 114)
  - Prints - UP Tiempo!, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 115)
  - Negatives - Berlin Billboard Project, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 116)
  - Prints - Berlin Billboard Project, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 117)
  - Negatives - Poets in the Bars, citywide, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 118)
  - Contact Sheets - Poets in the Bars, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 119)
  - Prints - Poets in the Bars, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 120)
  - Negatives - Light Site-ings: Holland Tunnel Drive-In Billboard, Holland Tunnel, Manhattan entrance, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 121)
  - Print - Light Site-ings: Holland Tunnel Drive-In Billboard, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 122)
  - Negatives - Automotive Votive, citywide, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 123)
  - Contact Sheets - Automotive Votive, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 124)
  - Prints - Automotive Votive, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 125)
  - Negatives - Kissing Doesn't Kill: Greed and Indifference Do, citywide, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 126)
  - Prints - Kissing Doesn't Kill: Greed and Indifference Do, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 127)
  - Negatives - Art in the Anchorage 6, Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 128)
  - Contact Sheets - Art in the Anchorage 6, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 129)
  - Prints - Art in the Anchorage 6, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 130)
  - Contact Sheets - Lincoln Center Out-of-Doors 1, 30 Lincoln Center Plaza, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 131)
  - Prints - Lincoln Center Out-of-Doors 1, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 132)
  - Negative - Video/Musica, 26 Avenue B, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 133)
  - Contact Sheets - Video/Musica, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 134)
  - Prints - Video/Musica, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 135)
  - Contact Sheets - What's in a Flame?, Cable Building, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 136)
  - Prints - What's in a Flame?, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 137)
  - Negative - All People with AIDS are Innocent, 466 Grand Street, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 138)
  - Prints - [Battery Park Maritime?], 1989 (Box 17, Folder 139)
  - Negatives - Demolish the Wall of Censorship rally, US Capitol Building, Washington DC, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 140)
  - Contact Sheets - Demolish the Wall of Censorship rally, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 141)
  - Prints - Demolish the Wall of Censorship rally, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 142)
  - Negatives - Creative Time at Dixon Place, 64 East 4th Street, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 143)
  - Contact Sheets - Creative Time at Dixon Place, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 144)
  - Prints - Creative Time at Dixon Place, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 145)
  - Contact Sheets - Black Sheep, 1st Avenue, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 146)
  - Prints - Black Sheep, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 147)
  - Prints - The Wilds and the Deep, Battery Maritime Building, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 148)
  - Negatives - Art in the Anchorage 7, Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 149)
  - Contact Sheets - Art in the Anchorage 7, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 150)
  - Prints - Art in the Anchorage 7 (continues in subsequent folder), 1990 (Box 18, Folder 151)
  - Prints - Art in the Anchorage 7 (continued from previous folder), 1990 (Box 18, Folder 152)
  - Negatives - Lincoln Center Out-of-Doors 2, 30 Lincoln Center Plaza, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 153)
  - Contact Sheets - Lincoln Center Out-of-Doors 2, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 154)
  - Prints - Lincoln Center Out-of-Doors 2, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 155)
  - Contact Sheets - Surgeon General's Warning, citywide, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 156)
  - Prints - Surgeon General's Warning, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 157)
  - Negatives - The Bowery Concert, Sara D. Roosevelt Park, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 158)
  - Contact Sheet - The Bowery Concert, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 159)